[{"answer": "No.  Did you", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I missed all of you.  We're okay, aren't we", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Well, you're a tower of support", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " We couldn't be on more solid ground", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " Is your script much like the novel? my friend says it's very good.  But you know, you read the novel, and then you see the movie", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I don't know why my friend, we've known each other how long..", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Nice to meet you", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "No, I don't think so", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Hi.  my friend and my friend", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Yes.  And you've met my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " I'm sure you understand", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Well today it was my friend.  And you should keep him away from our yard.  Because my friend will defend herself", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Oh, you know, I am", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "She'll never call again.  She called last week to tell me she'll never call again. Where's my friend", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I just wanted tonight to be with the people we love", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "They're not just our business managers, Panes", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Oh, okay, forgive me.  Your neighbors are here, for fuck's sake", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "It's not ruined, for fuck's sake.  It's one of your parties", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "\"How are you really doing, Panes", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "No.  No, not like the last time.  She was the rest of my life", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Like the last time", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Like the last time", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Shit, I forgot to call her back.  She's off on a trip somewhere.  Oh God, my grandad's flat in that place's been sold", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I should have damn well bought it.  Well, we can't afford it.  The movie's going to eat up a year of my life and I'm getting paid next to nothing.  Do you know how much my friend's getting?  Four million", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " How's the movie going?  Your movie.  You are making a movie, aren't you", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "That's it?  Yes.  Fine", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I never like to talk about my work", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "No.  Not something new", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Let me.  I'm my friend", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "And you know our friends, how", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "What was it?  What the fuck was it", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "my friend's novel", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Panes is not on my team anymore.  I'll have Panes if I like", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Dinner", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Okay, knock it off", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Truce", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I'm not going to leave you alone", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "They're nothing like us", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Well, you know...good days, bad days", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I meant my friend", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Why are you doing this", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": " But I am a possessive, fragile neurotic", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "my friend.  my friend's twent", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Scratch the two, write in a four", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Lemon or raspberry", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Lemon it is", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": " She left the fucking gate open", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Can't have gone far?  He's like a greyhound.  He could be miles away", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Not to mention my friend... my friend, come!", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Who doesn't know about the infamous composer's conference of 1948 where my friend persecuted the leaders of Soviet Music", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "my friend?  How the hell do you know about my friend", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "I'll tell you who doesn't know, cute girls don't know", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Who doesn't know about the infamous composer's conference of 1948 where my friend persecuted the leaders of Soviet Music", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Do Peter Sellers again", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Who the fuck do you think you are?  The part of my friend is not just about you. It's about every woman I've ever loved in my entire life.  Including my mother. The character is also clearly in her early twenties, my friend", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "Hello?  Last birthday was", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "This is insanity.  my friend..", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "Don't push me away", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "You're not ready", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "I wasn't part of that picture at all, was I?  I wasn't part of that decision.  Did I occur to you at all?  It's a fucking farce.  It's a fucking farce.  How long did you think you could keep it going. You're amazing.  Do you have any idea what you've done to us", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "I call that a perfect day", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "Damn near.  And a damn near perfect drug", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "You don't need to do that", "docId": "Anniversary-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "Relax.  You've done enough", "qsentId": 64}]